<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Josh Clark</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Josh Clark</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:39:49 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Pattern: Identifying Requests and Responses in Encrypted Traffic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:39:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-pattern/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Like a Doctor: Differential Diagnosis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/troubleshoot-like-a-doctor-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:29:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/troubleshoot-like-a-doctor-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The IT field is terrible at teaching people how to troubleshoot. Sure, if you got a CompTIA A+ or a CCNA, there were modules that talked about how to solve problems, but how much time did you actually spend on those modules? The CCNA course I took spent all of 5 minutes on it, with the message &amp;ldquo;there&amp;rsquo;s probably going to be a question that will ask what order these steps come in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converting Flask to Lambda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/converting-flask-to-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 11:27:05 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/converting-flask-to-lambda/</guid>
      <description>I’ve worked out how to convert a local Flask app to AWS Lambda without having to involve extra modules, vendors, or middleware.&#xA;Introduction Moving products from a prototype to a deployment can be tricky. In particular, I find myself writing small Flask apps for every little problem, and trying to deploy them to Lambda involves putting an entire layer of abstraction on top of them.&#xA;Surveying the landscape, there seems to be one model of providing a developer a CLI tool that builds and deploys the entire project:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
